<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="lockscreen_strings_backup_question_1_txt">"What is your mother's maiden name?"</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_strings_backup_question_3_txt">What is your favourite place?</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_strings_backup_question_4_txt">What is your favourite film?</string>
    <string name="internal_storage_erase_data_desc">Are you sure you want to format internal storage? All data on it will be lost.</string>
    <string name="mmiFdnError">Operation is restricted to fixed dialling numbers only.</string>
    <string name="shutdown_progress">Shutting down…</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_costMoney">Allow applications to do things that can cost you money.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_messages">Read and write your SMS, e-mail, and other messages.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_personalInfo">Direct access to your contacts and calendar stored on the phone.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_network">Allow applications to access various network features.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_hardwareControls">Direct access to hardware on the handset.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_phoneCalls">Monitor, record, and process phone calls.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_systemTools">Lower-level access and control of the system.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_developmentTools">Features only needed for application developers.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_storage">Access the internal storage</string>
    <string name="permdesc_statusBar">Allows application to disable the status bar or add and remove system icons.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_expandStatusBar">Allows application to expand or collapse the status bar.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_processOutgoingCalls">Allows application to process outgoing calls and change the number to be dialed. Malicious applications may monitor, redirect, or prevent outgoing calls.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveSms">Allows application to receive and process SMS messages. Malicious applications may monitor your messages or delete them without showing them to you.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveMms">Allows application to receive and process MMS messages. Malicious applications may monitor your messages or delete them without showing them to you.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveEmergencyBroadcast">Allows application to receive and process emergency broadcast messages. This permission is only available to system applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_sendSms">Allows application to send SMS messages. Malicious applications may cost you money by sending messages without your confirmation.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_sendSmsNoConfirmation">Allows application to send SMS messages. Malicious applications may cost you money by sending messages without your confirmation.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readSms">Allows application to read SMS messages stored on your phone or SIM card. Malicious applications may read your confidential messages.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeSms">Allows application to write to SMS messages stored on your phone or SIM card. Malicious applications may delete your messages.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveWapPush">Allows application to receive and process WAP messages. Malicious applications may monitor your messages or delete them without showing them to you.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_getTasks">Allows application to retrieve information about currently and recently running tasks. May allow malicious applications to discover private information about other applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_reorderTasks">Allows an application to move tasks to the foreground and background. Malicious applications can force themselves to the front without your control.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_removeTasks">Allows an application to remove tasks and kill their applications. Malicious applications can disrupt the behaviour of other applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setDebugApp">Allows an application to turn on debugging for another application. Malicious applications can use this to kill other applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeConfiguration">Allows an application to change the current configuration, such as the locale or overall font size.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_enableCarMode">Allows an application to enable the car mode.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_killBackgroundProcesses">"Allows an application to kill background processes of other applications, even if memory isn't low."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_forceStopPackages">Allows an application to forcibly stop other applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_forceBack">Allows an application to force any activity that is in the foreground to close and go back. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_dump">Allows application to retrieve internal state of the system. Malicious applications may retrieve a wide variety of private and secure information that they should never normally need.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_retrieve_window_content">Allows application to retrieve the content of the active window. Malicious applications may retrieve the entire window content and examine all its text except passwords.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_shutdown">Puts the activity manager into a shutdown state. Does not perform a complete shutdown.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_stopAppSwitches">Prevents the user from switching to another application.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_runSetActivityWatcher">Allows an application to monitor and control how the system launches activities. Malicious applications may completely compromise the system. This permission is only needed for development, never for normal use.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_broadcastPackageRemoved">Allows an application to broadcast a notification that an application package has been removed. Malicious applications may use this to kill any other running application.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_broadcastSmsReceived">Allows an application to broadcast a notification that an SMS message has been received. Malicious applications may use this to forge incoming SMS messages.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_broadcastWapPush">Allows an application to broadcast a notification that a WAP PUSH message has been received. Malicious applications may use this to forge MMS message receipt or to silently replace the content of any web page with malicious variants.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setProcessLimit">Allows an application to control the maximum number of processes that will run. Never needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setAlwaysFinish">Allows an application to control whether activities are always finished as soon as they go to the background. Never needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_batteryStats">Allows the modification of collected battery statistics. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_backup">"Allows the application to control the system's backup and restore mechanism. Not for use by normal applications."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_confirm_full_backup">Allows the application to launch the full backup confirmation UI. Not to be used by any application.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_internalSystemWindow">Allows the creation of windows that are intended to be used by the internal system user interface. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_systemAlertWindow">Allows an application to show system alert windows. Malicious applications can take over the entire screen.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setAnimationScale">Allows an application to change the global animation speed (faster or slower animations) at any time.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_manageAppTokens">Allows applications to create and manage their own tokens, bypassing their normal Z-ordering. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_injectEvents">Allows an application to deliver its own input events (key presses, etc.) to other applications. Malicious applications can use this to take over the phone.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readInputState">Allows applications to watch the keys you press even when interacting with another application (such as entering a password). Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindInputMethod">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of an input method. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindTextService">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a text service(e.g. SpellCheckerService). Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindVpnService">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a Vpn service. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindWallpaper">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a wallpaper. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindRemoteViews">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a widget service. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindDeviceAdmin">Allows the holder to send intents to a device administrator. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setOrientation">Allows an application to change the rotation of the screen at any time. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setPointerSpeed">Allows an application to change the mouse or trackpad pointer speed at any time. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_signalPersistentProcesses">Allows application to request that the supplied signal be sent to all persistent processes.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_persistentActivity">"Allows an application to make parts of itself persistent, so the system can't use it for other applications."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_deletePackages">Allows an application to delete Android packages. Malicious applications can use this to delete important applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_deleteCacheFiles">Allows an application to delete cache files.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_getPackageSize">Allows an application to retrieve its code, data, and cache sizes</string>
    <string name="permdesc_installPackages">Allows an application to install new or updated Android packages. Malicious applications can use this to add new applications with arbitrarily powerful permissions.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_clearAppCache">Allows an application to free phone storage by deleting files in application cache directory. Access is very restricted usually to system process.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readLogs">"Allows an application to read from the system's various log files. This allows it to discover general information about what you are doing with the phone, potentially including personal or private information."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_anyCodecForPlayback">Allows an application to use any installed media decoder to decode for playback.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_diagnostic">Allows an application to read and write to any resource owned by the diag group; for example, files in /dev. This could potentially affect system stability and security. This should be ONLY be used for hardware-specific diagnostics by the manufacturer or operator.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeComponentState">"Allows an application to change whether a component of another application is enabled or not. Malicious applications can use this to disable important phone capabilities. Care must be used with this permission, as it is possible to get application components into an unusable, inconsistent or unstable state. "</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setPreferredApplications">Allows an application to modify your preferred applications. This can allow malicious applications to silently change the applications that are run, spoofing your existing applications to collect private data from you.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeSettings">"Allows an application to modify the system's settings data. Malicious applications can corrupt your system's configuration."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeSecureSettings">"Allows an application to modify the system's secure settings data. Not for use by normal applications."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeGservices">Allows an application to modify the Google services map. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveBootCompleted">Allows an application to start itself as soon as the system has finished booting. This can make it take longer to start the phone and allow the application to slow down the phone overall by always running.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_broadcastSticky">Allows an application to send sticky broadcasts, which remain after the broadcast ends. Malicious applications can make the phone slow or unstable by causing it to use too much memory.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readContacts">Allows an application to read all of the contact (address) data stored on your phone. Malicious applications can use this to send your data to other people.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeContacts">Allows an application to modify the contact (address) data stored on your phone. Malicious applications can use this to erase or modify your contact data.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readProfile">Allows the application to read personal profile information stored on your device, such as your name and contact information. This means the application can identify you and send your profile information to others.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeProfile">Allows the application to change or add to personal profile information stored on your device, such as your name and contact information. This means other applications can identify you and send your profile information to others.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readSocialStream">Allows the application to access and sync social updates from you and your friends. Malicious apps can use this to read private communications between you and your friends on social networks.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeSocialStream">Allows the application to display social updates from your friends. Malicious apps can use this to pretend to be a friend and trick you into revealing passwords or other confidential information.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readCalendar">"Allows an application to read all calendar events stored on your phone, including those of friends or co-workers. A malicious application with this permission can extract personal information from these calendars without the owners' knowledge."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeCalendar">"Allows an application to send event invitations as the calendar owner and add, remove, change events that you can modify on your device, including those of friends or co-workers. A malicious application with this permission can send spam emails that appear to come from calendar owners, modify events without the owners' knowledge, or add fake events."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessMockLocation">Create mock location sources for testing. Malicious applications can use this to override the location and/or status returned by real location sources such as GPS or Network providers.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessLocationExtraCommands">Access extra location provider commands. Malicious applications could use this to interfere with the operation of the GPS or other location sources.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_installLocationProvider">Create mock location sources for testing. Malicious applications can use this to override the location and/or status returned by real location sources such as GPS or Network providers or monitor and report your location to an external source.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessFineLocation">Access fine location sources such as the Global Positioning System on the phone, where available. Malicious applications can use this to determine where you are, and may consume additional battery power.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessCoarseLocation">Access coarse location sources such as the cellular network database to determine an approximate phone location, where available. Malicious applications can use this to determine approximately where you are.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessSurfaceFlinger">Allows application to use SurfaceFlinger low-level features.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readFrameBuffer">Allows application to read the content of the frame buffer.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_modifyAudioSettings">Allows application to modify global audio settings such as volume and routing.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_recordAudio">Allows application to access the audio record path.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_camera">Allows application to take pictures and videos with the camera. This allows the application at any time to collect images the camera is seeing.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_brick">Allows the application to disable the entire phone permanently. This is very dangerous.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_reboot">Allows the application to force the phone to reboot.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_mount_unmount_filesystems">Allows the application to mount and unmount filesystems for removable storage.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_vibrate">Allows the application to control the vibrator.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_flashlight">Allows the application to control the flashlight.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_hardware_test">Allows the application to control various peripherals for the purpose of hardware testing.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_callPhone">Allows the application to call phone numbers without your intervention. Malicious applications may cause unexpected calls on your phone bill. Note that this does not allow the application to call emergency numbers.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_callPrivileged">Allows the application to call any phone number, including emergency numbers, without your intervention. Malicious applications may place unnecessary and illegal calls to emergency services.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_performCdmaProvisioning">Allows the application to start CDMA provisioning. Malicious applications may unnecessarily start CDMA provisioning</string>
    <string name="permdesc_locationUpdates">Allows enabling/disabling location update notifications from the radio. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_checkinProperties">Allows read/write access to properties uploaded by the checkin service. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindGadget">Allows the application to tell the system which widgets can be used by which application. With this permission, applications can give access to personal data to other applications. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_modifyPhoneState">Allows the application to control the phone features of the device. An application with this permission can switch networks, turn the phone radio on and off and the like without ever notifying you.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readPhoneState">Allows the application to access the phone features of the device. An application with this permission can determine the phone number and serial number of this phone, whether a call is active, the number that call is connected to and the like.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_wakeLock">Allows an application to prevent the phone from going to sleep.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_devicePower">Allows the application to turn the phone on or off.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_factoryTest">Run as a low-level manufacturer test, allowing complete access to the phone hardware. Only available when a phone is running in manufacturer test mode.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setWallpaper">Allows the application to set the system wallpaper.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setWallpaperHints">Allows the application to set the system wallpaper size hints.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_masterClear">Allows an application to completely reset the system to its factory settings, erasing all data, configuration, and installed applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setTime">"Allows an application to change the phone's clock time."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setTimeZone">"Allows an application to change the phone's time zone."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accountManagerService">Allows an application to make calls to AccountAuthenticators</string>
    <string name="permdesc_getAccounts">Allows an application to get the list of accounts known by the phone.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_authenticateAccounts">Allows an application to use the account authenticator capabilities of the AccountManager, including creating accounts and getting and setting their passwords.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_manageAccounts">Allows an application to perform operations like adding, and removing accounts and deleting their password.</string>
    <string name="permlab_useCredentials">use the authentication credentials of an account</string>
    <string name="permdesc_useCredentials">Allows an application to request authentication tokens.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessNetworkState">Allows an application to view the state of all networks.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_createNetworkSockets">Allows an application to create network sockets.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeApnSettings">Allows an application to change network settings and to intercept and inspect all network traffic, for example to change the proxy and port of any APN. Malicious applications could monitor, redirect or modify network packets without your knowledge.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeNetworkState">Allows an application to change the state of network connectivity.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeTetherState">Allows an application to change the state of tethered network connectivity.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeBackgroundDataSetting">Allows an application to change the background data usage setting.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessWifiState">Allows an application to view the information about the state of Wi-Fi.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeWifiState">Allows an application to connect to and disconnect from Wi-Fi access points, and to make changes to configured Wi-Fi networks.</string>
    <string name="permlab_changeWifiMulticastState">allow Wi-Fi Multicast reception</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeWifiMulticastState">Allows an application to receive packets not directly addressed to your device. This can be useful when discovering services offered near by. It uses more power than the non-multicast mode.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessWimaxState">Allows an application to view information about the state of WiMAX.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeWimaxState">Allows an application to connect to and disconnect from WiMAX network.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bluetoothAdmin">Allows an application to configure the local Bluetooth phone, and to discover and pair with remote devices.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bluetooth">Allows an application to view configuration of the local Bluetooth phone, and to make and accept connections with paired devices.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_nfc">Allows an application to communicate with Near Field Communication (NFC) tags, cards and readers.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_disableKeyguard">Allows an application to disable the keylock and any associated password security. A legitimate example of this is the phone disabling the keylock when receiving an incoming phone call, then re-enabling the keylock when the call is finished.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readSyncSettings">Allows an application to read the sync settings, such as whether sync is enabled for Contacts.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeSyncSettings">Allows an application to modify the sync settings, such as whether sync is enabled for Contacts.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readSyncStats">Allows an application to read the sync stats; e.g., the history of syncs that have occurred.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_subscribedFeedsWrite">Allows an application to modify your currently synced feeds. This could allow a malicious application to change your synced feeds.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readDictionary">Allows an application to read any private words, names and phrases that the user may have stored in the user dictionary.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeDictionary">Allows an application to write new words into the user dictionary.</string>
    <string name="permlab_cache_filesystem">access the cache file system</string>
    <string name="permdesc_cache_filesystem">Allows an application to read and write the cache file system.</string>
    <string name="policydesc_limitPassword">Control the length and the characters allowed in screen-unlock passwords</string>
    <string name="policydesc_watchLogin">"Monitor the number of incorrect passwords entered when unlocking the screen, and lock the phone or erase all the phone's data if too many incorrect passwords are entered"</string>
    <string name="policydesc_wipeData">"Erase the phone's data without warning, by performing a factory data reset"</string>
    <string name="policydesc_setGlobalProxy">Set the device global proxy to be used while policy is enabled. Only the first device admin sets the effective global proxy.</string>
    <string name="policydesc_expirePassword">Control how frequently the lock-screen password must be changed</string>
    <string name="policydesc_encryptedStorage">"Require that stored application data be encrypted "</string>
    <string name="emailTypeMobile">Mobile</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_permanent_disabled_sim_instructions">"Your SIM card is permanently disabled.
Please contact your wireless service provider to obtain another SIM card."</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_sim_unlock_progress_dialog_message">Unlocking SIM card…</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_too_many_failed_attempts_dialog_message" formatted="false">"You have incorrectly drawn your unlock pattern %d times. 

Please try again in %d seconds."</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_too_many_failed_password_attempts_dialog_message" formatted="false">"You have incorrectly entered your password %d times. 

Please try again in %d seconds."</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_too_many_failed_pin_attempts_dialog_message" formatted="false">"You have incorrectly entered your PIN %d times. 

Please try again in %d seconds."</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_failed_attempts_almost_glogin" formatted="false">"You have incorrectly drawn your unlock pattern %d times. After %d more unsuccessful attempts, you will be asked to unlock your phone using your Google sign-in.

Please try again in %d seconds."</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_failed_attempts_almost_at_wipe" formatted="false">You have incorrectly attempted to unlock the phone %d times. After %d more unsuccessful attempts, the phone will be reset to factory default and all user data will be lost.</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_failed_attempts_now_wiping">You have incorrectly attempted to unlock the phone %d times. The phone will now be reset to factory default.</string>
    <string name="factorytest_not_system">The FACTORY_TEST action is only supported for packages installed in /system/app.</string>
    <string name="factorytest_no_action">No package was found that provides the FACTORY_TEST action.</string>
    <string name="autofill_province">County</string>
    <string name="autofill_state">County</string>
    <string name="autofill_zip_code">Post code</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readHistoryBookmarks">"Allows the application to read all the URLs that the Browser has visited, and all of the Browser's bookmarks."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeHistoryBookmarks">"Allows an application to modify the Browser's history or bookmarks stored on your phone. Malicious applications can use this to erase or modify your Browser's data."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setAlarm">Allows the application to set an alarm in an installed alarm clock application. Some alarm clock applications may not implement this feature.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_addVoicemail">Allows the application to add messages to your voicemail inbox.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeGeolocationPermissions">"Allows an application to modify the Browser's geolocation permissions. Malicious applications can use this to allow sending location information to arbitrary websites."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_packageVerificationAgent">Allows the application to verify a package is installable.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindPackageVerifier">Allows the holder to make requests of package verifiers. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="replace">Replace…</string>
    <string name="clearDefaultHintMsg">Clear default in Settings > Apps.</string>
    <string name="aerr_process">Unfortunately, the process %1$s has stopped.</string>
    <string name="smv_application">The application %1$s (process %2$s) has violated its self-enforced StrictMode policy.</string>
    <string name="smv_process">The process %1$s has violated its self-enforced StrictMode policy.</string>
    <string name="android_upgrading_apk">Optimising application %1$d of %2$d.</string>
    <string name="heavy_weight_switcher_text">Another application is already running that must be stopped before you can start a new one.</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_pbc_go_negotiation_request_message">Wi-Fi Direct connection setup request from %1$s. Click OK to accept.</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_pin_go_negotiation_request_message">Wi-Fi Direct connection setup request from %1$s. Enter pin to proceed.</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_pin_display_message">WPS pin %1$s needs to be entered on the peer device %2$s for connection setup to proceed</string>
    <string name="usb_storage_error_message">There is a problem with using your internal storage for USB mass storage.</string>
    <string name="usb_storage_stop_message">Before turning off USB storage, make sure that you have unmounted (“ejected”) your Android‘s internal storage from your computer.</string>
    <string name="extmedia_format_message">Are you sure that you want to format the SD card? All data on your card will be lost.</string>
    <string name="ext_media_nofs_notification_message">SD card blank or has unsupported file system.</string>
    <string name="ext_media_badremoval_notification_title">SD card removed unexpectedly</string>
    <string name="ext_media_safe_unmount_notification_message">You can safely remove SD card.</string>
    <string name="permlab_copyProtectedData">Allows invoking default container service to copy content. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_copyProtectedData">Allows invoking of default container service to copy content. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="grant_credentials_permission_message_header">The following one or more applications request permission to access your account, both now and in the future.</string>
    <string name="format_error">Failed to erase SD card.</string>
    <string name="description_direction_left">Left for %s.</string>
    <string name="org_name">Organisation:</string>
    <string name="org_unit">Organisational unit:</string>
    <string name="list_delimeter">", "</string>
    <string name="init_strings_init_mode_title_txt">Initialisation mode</string>
    <string name="init_strings_dialog_make_sure_title_txt">Initialising phone</string>
    <string name="init_strings_dialog_battery_low_msg_txt">The battery is not enough to execute initialisation. Try again after charge.</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_strings_sim_puk_locked_message_txt">Enter the PUK code from your operator</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_strings_sim_puk_locked_out_message_txt">Please contact your operator</string>
    <string name="seport_strings_accessory_not_supported_txt">Headset not supported. Use another headset or visit the Sony Mobile support site for more information.</string>
    <string name="ct_cplusw_notification_text">You have accessed CT’s WiFi network. For billing info, please consult 10000 or your local CT business hall. Please disconnect when you aren’t using it.</string>
    <string name="policydesc_allowHtmlEmail">Set whether the emails synchronised to your phone can be in HTML format or just plain text</string>
    <string name="policydesc_controlCamera">"Control the usage of your phone's built-in camera"</string>
    <string name="policydesc_maximumCalendarAgeFilte">Set the maximum number of days that past calendars can be synchronised to your phone</string>
    <string name="policydesc_maximumEmailAge">Set the maximum number of days that past emails can be synchronised to your phone</string>
    <string name="policydesc_maximumEmailBodySize">Set the maximum size beyond which email messages are truncated when they are synchronised to your phone</string>
</resources>
